Dorothy Ruggles Richter Papers MS150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dorothy Ruggles Richter Papers
1935 -- 1987
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Ruggles, Dorothy Richter
MS150
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Biographical / Historical
Dorothy Ruggles graduated from Tufts College with a BA in English in 1937. While at Tufts she served as a Jackson class officer. Ruggles worked with N.E.T.&T. for 10 years and moved to Florida in 1950. In Florida she taught for 10 years and earned an MA from Florida State University in Library Science. She was an elementary and high school librarian for 22 years. Ruggles married Morris Richter. They had two children.
Custodial History
Received by DCA from the Gift Planning Office.
Scope and Contents
This collection includes ephemera from Ruggles' time at Tufts College such as class day programs, newspaper clippings, dramatic production programs, and receipts. It also includes materials from Class of 1937 reunions, photographs and an audiocassette of Dr. Robert L. Nichols speaking at Alumni Day, May 21, 1977.
Alumni collections; University history; Tufts University -- History; Jackson College for Women (Tufts University)
- Papers, 1935 -- 1987; 1936 -- 1937; MS150.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes ephemera from Richter's time at Tufts College such as class day programs, newspaper clippings, dramatic production programs and receipts. It also includes materials from Class of 1937 reunions, photographs and an audio cassette of Dr. Robert L. Nichols speaking at Alumni Day, May 21, 1977.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Accounts Book, 1935; MS150.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Class Day program, Tree Day and Jackson Regulations, 1936; MS150.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Bursar receipts, 1936 -- 1937; MS150.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Play and performance programs, 1936 -- 1937; MS150.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Class Day 1937 programs, MS150.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Senior Banquet program, 1937; MS150.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College Alumni Bulletin, 1937; MS150.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    In Memory of John Albert Cousens, December 1937
  - Newspaper clippings, 1935 -- 1937; MS150.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Tufts University Library groundbreaking souvenir envelope, 1962; MS150.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Traditions at Tufts, 3rd Edition, 1967; MS150.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clipping, 1976; MS150.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    Jean Mayer and nutrition
  - Fortieth reunion materials, 1977; MS150.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    Includes undated photographs
  - Alumni Day speech, Robert L. Nichols, 1977-05-21; MS150.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    audiocassette
  - High on the Hill, Tufts Then and Now, 1979; MS150.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Newspaper clipping, 1983; MS150.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    Goddard Chapel
  - Fiftieth Reunion materials, 1987; MS150.001.001.00016 (Box 1)